{
    "subject": "resource/Call_of_Duty:_Black_Ops_III",
    "predicate": "ontology/gameEngine",
    "object": "resource/IW_engine",
    "human_readable": "The game engine of Call of Duty: Black Ops III is IW engine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.913753867149353,
            "question": "What is the name of the game engine used in Call of Duty: Black Ops III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8762109279632568,
            "question": "What game engine powers Call of Duty: Black Ops III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7837325930595398,
            "question": "Which game engine did Treyarch develop for Call of Duty: Black Ops III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.722805917263031,
            "question": "What other games use the IW engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7176562547683716,
            "question": "Is IW engine a proprietary game engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.62105393409729,
            "question": "Has the IW engine been used in any other Call of Duty titles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6121786832809448,
            "question": "Who developed the IW engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.552709698677063,
            "question": "How does the IW engine compare to other popular game engines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5381702780723572,
            "question": "What are some of the key features of the IW engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4370480179786682,
            "question": "What are the advantages of using the IW engine for game development?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The game engine of Call of Duty: Black Ops III is IW engine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6341_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the key features of the IW engine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6341_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the IW engine compare to other popular game engines?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6341_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who developed the IW engine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6341_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6341_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the game engine used by various games in the Call of Duty series. Specifically, files 11.txt and 19.txt mention that the IW Engine is a game engine developed by Infinity Ward, based on id Tech 3, which was first used on the highly successful game Call of Duty 2. The documents also mention that this engine has been continually upgraded and used on several games in the series, including Call of Duty: Black Ops.\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that the game engine of Call of Duty: Black Ops III is indeed the IW Engine."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents confirm that the IW Engine was used for the development of Call of Duty: Black Ops III. Therefore, the statement \"The game engine of Call of Duty: Black Ops III is IW engine\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}